Guide to the Stanford Historical Photograph Collection
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Biographical Photographs, Series 3
  - Northway, William H. Jr. (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Oaks, Clinton (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - O'Brien, Richard F. (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - O'Connor, Sandra Day (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - O'Dell, William R. (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Ogg, Richard A., Jr. (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - Oglesby, Clarkson H. (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - Olds, Arnold E. (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - Olmsted, Frederick Law (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - O'Malley, Charles D. (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - Ophuls, William (Box 19, Folder 29)
  - Orcutt, William W. (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - Osborne, George E. (Box 19, Folder 31)
  - Oskison, John M. (Box 19, Folder 32)
  - Owens, William B. (Box 19, Folder 33)
  - Oxley, Gail M. (Box 19, Folder 34)
  - Pabst, Marjorie Allen (Mrs. William) (Box 19, Folder 35)
  - Packard, David (Box 19, Folder 36)
  - Packard, Lucile Salter (Mrs. David) (Box 19, Folder 37)
  - Packard, Mabel (Box 19, Folder 38)
  - Packer, Herbert (Box 19, Folder 39)
  - Page, Robert M. (Box 19, Folder 40)
  - Palmateer, Theron J. (Box 19, Folder 41)
  - Panofsky, Wolfgang K. J. (Box 19, Folder 42)
  - Park, Charles F. (Box 19, Folder 43)
  - Parkin, William M. (Box 19, Folder 44)
  - Parks, Charles H. (Box 19, Folder 45)
  - Parks, George A. (Box 19, Folder 46)
  - Parks, George S. (Box 19, Folder 47)
  - Parton, Floyd A. (Box 19, Folder 48)
  - Pauling, Linus (Box 19, Folder 49)
  - Paulson, B. (Box 19, Folder 50)
  - Payton, Sallyanne (Box 19, Folder 51)
  - Pearson, Daryl (Box 19, Folder 52)
  - Pease, Ernest M. (Box 19, Folder 53)
  - Pease, Otis A. (Box 19, Folder 54)
  - Pederson, Carlton A. (Box 19, Folder 55)
  - Pederson, Donald O. (Box 19, Folder 56)
  - Peirce, George James (and Mrs.) (Box 19, Folder 57)
  - Pemberton, John R. "Bill" (Box 19, Folder 58)
  - Percy, Senator Charles (Box 19, Folder 59)
  - Perkins, William A., Jr. (Box 19, Folder 60)
  - Perrine, Frederic A. C. (Box 19, Folder 61)
  - Perry, Ruth (Box 19, Folder 62)
  - Peters, Lucy Upton (Box 19, Folder 63)
  - Peterson, Allen M. (Box 19, Folder 64)
  - Peterson, Harry C. (Box 19, Folder 65)
  - Peterson, Julius E. (Box 19, Folder 66)
  - Peterson, Mary Hulda (Box 19, Folder 67)
  - Petree, Neil H. (Box 19, Folder 68)
  - Pettit, Joseph M. (Box 19, Folder 69)
  - Philbrick, Norman D. (Box 19, Folder 70)
  - Phillips, Donald A. (Box 19, Folder 71)
  - Phillips, John Pressley Jr. (Box 19, Folder 72)
  - Phleger, Herman (Box 19, Folder 73)
  - Picher, Oliver S. (Box 19, Folder 74)
  - Pigott, Paul R. (Box 19, Folder 75)
  - Pike, Thomas P. (Box 19, Folder 76)
  - Pings, Cornelius J., Jr. (Box 19, Folder 77)
  - Pitcher, Louise (Box 19, Folder 78)
  - Pitzer, Kenneth S. (and Mrs.) 6th President of Stanford (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Pitzer, Kenneth S.--Inauguration (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Pitzer, Kenneth S.--Resignation Press Conference (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Platt, Alan (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Plumb, Jane (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Polhemus, James H. (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Pomeroy, John N. (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Pompidou, Georges (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Pond, Samuel A. (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Ponzer, Ernest W. (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Popper, Jan (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Porterfield, James T. S. (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Posin, Jack A. (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Post, Seraphim F. (Dynie) (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Potter, David M. (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Potter, Margaret (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Pound, Roscoe (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Powell, Richard R. B. (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Powers, Dennis (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Powers, Harry H. (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Powers, Nadine Malm (Mrs. James) (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Prescott, Carlos (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - Pribram, Karl H. (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - Price, George Clinton (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - Price, Harry (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - Price, William W. (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - Prichard, Jean DeForest (Mrs. William A.) (Box 21, Folder 27)
  - Prichard, William A. (Box 21, Folder 28)
  - Prince, Kenneth J. (Box 21, Folder 29)
  - Prior, Joseph C. (Box 21, Folder 30)
  - Pryor, Helen B. (Box 21, Folder 31)
  - Pugh, Edmund W. (Box 21, Folder 32)
  - Purdue, Albert H. (Box 21, Folder 33)
  - Putz, John L. (Box 21, Folder 34)
  - Quate, Calvin F. (Box 21, Folder 35)
  - Quillen, I. James (Box 21, Folder 36)
  - Raish, Ralph R. (Box 21, Folder 37)
  - Rambo, William R. (Box 21, Folder 38)
  - Ramey, Henry, Jr. (Box 21, Folder 39)
  - Rathbun, Harry J. (and family) (Box 21, Folder 40)
  - Rather, Lelland J. (Box 21, Folder 41)
  - Redfield, Robert (Box 21, Folder 42)
  - Redlich, Joseph (Box 21, Folder 43)
  - Regnery, David C. (and Mrs.) (Box 21, Folder 44)
  - Rehnquist, William H. (Box 21, Folder 45)
  - Reid, Elliott G. (Box 21, Folder 46)
  - Reid, Louis A. (Box 21, Folder 47)
  - Reid. Whitelaw (Box 21, Folder 48)
  - Reinhardt, Aurelia (Box 21, Folder 49)
  - Reinhardt, Kurt F. (Box 21, Folder 50)
  - Reining, Charles (Box 21, Folder 51)
  - Remele, Carol (Box 21, Folder 52)
  - Rendtorff, Karl Gustau (and Family) (Box 21, Folder 53)
  - Repass, Merle M. (Box 21, Folder 54)
  - Reynolds, Charles N. (Box 21, Folder 55)
  - Reynolds, Harry B. (and Mrs.) (Box 21, Folder 56)
  - Reynolds, Herbert (Box 21, Folder 57)
  - Reynolds, Jackson E. (Box 21, Folder 59)
  - Reynolds, Leon B. (Box 21, Folder 60)
  - Reynolds, James M. (Box 21, Folder 61)
  - Rhinelander, Philip H. (Box 21, Folder 62)
  - Riasanousky, Alex (Box 21, Folder 63)
  - Rich, Ellsworth L. (Box 21, Folder 64)
  - Rich, Ernest I. (Box 21, Folder 65)
  - Rich, Willis H. (Box 21, Folder 66)
  - Richardson, Eri H. (Box 21, Folder 67)
  - Richardson, George Mann (Box 21, Folder 68)
  - Rickard, Edgar (Box 21, Folder 69)
  - Ringressy, Grace E. (Box 21, Folder 70)
  - Riter, George W. (Box 21, Folder 71)
  - Rivers, William L. (Box 21, Folder 72)
  - Robertson, Donald L. (Box 21, Folder 73)
  - Robichek, Alexander A. (Box 21, Folder 74)
  - Robinson, Edgar Eugene (Box 21, Folder 75)
  - Robles, Secundi (Box 21, Folder 76)
  - Rockefeller, Sharon Percy (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Rockhold, John E. (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Rogers, Alice (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Rogers, Austin Flint (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Rogers, Frederick John (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Rogers, Rutherford D. (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Rogers, Will, Jr. (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Rogers, William L. (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Rogow, Arnold (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Roosevelt, Theodore (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Rosaldo, Michelle (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Rose, Hugh (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Roseberry, Louis H. (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Rosenbaum, Lee (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Rosenberg, Abraham (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Rosencranz, Armin (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Rosenzweig, Robert (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Ross, Edward A. (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Ross, John M. (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Ross, Perley A. (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Rosse, James (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Rosseter, Myrtle Bruce (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Roth, Almon E. (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - Roth, Earl F. (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - Rothwell, C. Easton (Box 22, Folder 25)
  - Rottschaefer, Henry (Box 22, Folder 26)
  - Royden, Halsey (Box 22, Folder 27)
  - Ruch, Marian S. (Box 22, Folder 28)
  - Rundell, Oliver S. (Box 22, Folder 29)
  - Runyan, Guyla (Box 22, Folder 30)
  - Ruppenthal, Karl M. (Box 22, Folder 31)
  - Rusmore, Jay T. (Box 22, Folder 32)
  - Russell, Frances Theresa (Box 22, Folder 33)
  - Ryan, Harris J. (and Mrs.) (Box 22, Folder 34)
  - Rytand, David A. (Box 22, Folder 35)
  - Ryus, David D. III (Box 22, Folder 36)
  - Salgo, Sandor (Box 22, Folder 37)
  - Sampson, Martin W. (Box 22, Folder 38)
  - Sanchez, Nellie Van De Grift (Box 22, Folder 39)
  - Sandwick, Richard L. (Box 22, Folder 40)
  - Sanford, Fernando (Box 22, Folder 41)
  - Savelle, Maxwell H. (Box 22, Folder 42)
  - Sawyer, Lorenzo (Box 22, Folder 43)
  - Scelle, Georges (Box 22, Folder 44)
  - Schallenberger, Margaret E. (Box 22, Folder 45)
  - Schanch, F. Raber (Box 22, Folder 46)
  - Schaupp, Karl (Box 22, Folder 47)
  - Schiff, Leonard (and Mrs.) (Box 22, Folder 48)
  - Schimke, Robert T. (Box 22, Folder 49)
  - Schlick, Moritz (Box 22, Folder 50)
  - Schmidt, Harold C. (Box 22, Folder 51)
  - Schopbach, Leonore (Box 22, Folder 52)
  - Schultz, Edwin W. (Box 22, Folder 53)
  - Schwartz, John J. (Box 22, Folder 54)
  - Schwarzenbek, Frank X. (Box 22, Folder 55)
  - Scofield, Norman Bishop (Box 22, Folder 56)
  - Seale, Jessie D. Carr (Box 22, Folder 57)
  - Searles, Colbert (and children) (Box 22, Folder 58)
  - Sears, Harry Johnson (Box 22, Folder 59)
  - Sears, Jesse Brundage (Box 22, Folder 60)
  - Sears, Kenneth C. (Box 22, Folder 61)
  - Sears, Robert (Box 22, Folder 62)
  - Seashore, Robert H. (Box 22, Folder 63)
  - Seem, Ralph B. (Box 22, Folder 64)
  - Segerstrom, William F. (Box 22, Folder 65)
  - Sellards, John A. (Box 22, Folder 66)
  - Sensabaugh, George F. (Box 22, Folder 67)
  - Sessions, Sterling D. (Box 22, Folder 68)
  - Sevareid, Eric (Box 22, Folder 69)
  - Seward, George L. (Box 22, Folder 70)
  - Seward, Samuel S. (Box 22, Folder 71)
  - Seymour, Charles (Box 22, Folder 72)
  - Shafer, George D. (Box 22, Folder 73)
  - Shallenberger, Frank K. (Box 22, Folder 74)
  - Sharp, Frank C. (Box 22, Folder 75)
  - Shaw, Edward S. (Box 22, Folder 76)
  - Shaw, Walter R. (Box 22, Folder 77)
  - Shedd, Solon (Box 22, Folder 78)
  - Sheehan, John F. (Box 22, Folder 79)
  - Sheldon, Henry D. (Box 22, Folder 80)
  - Shepard, Charles E. (Box 22, Folder 81)
  - Shepherd, Grace (Box 22, Folder 82)
  - Shockley, William B. (Box 22, Folder 83)
  - Shoup, Jack W. (Box 22, Folder 84)
  - Shoup, Paul (and Mr. and Mrs. Guy Shoup) (Box 22, Folder 85)
  - Show, Arley Barthlow (Box 22, Folder 86)
  - Sibley, Mulford (Box 22, Folder 87)
  - Siegman, Anthony E. (Box 22, Folder 88)
  - Siena, James W. (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Simmons, Samuel E. (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Simpson, Claude (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Skilling, Hugh H. (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Skogsberg, Tage (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Sloan, William Henry (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Slonaker, James R. (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Sloss, Leon, Jr. (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Sloss, M. C. (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Smith, Albert W. (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Smith, Gilbert Morgan (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Smith, James H. C. (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Smith, James Perrin (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Smith, Kendric C. (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Smith, Marion M. (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Smith, Mary Roberts (Mrs. Albert W. Smith. Later Mrs. Dane Coolidge) (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Smith, May Hurlburt (Mrs. Everett) (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Smith, N. T. (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Smith, Philip (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Smith, Ralph J. (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - Smith, Stanley A. (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Snyder, John Otterbein (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - Snyder, Rixford K. (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - Sokol, Anthony E. (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - Solomon, Ezra (Box 23, Folder 25)
  - Sonkin, Simon (Box 23, Folder 26)
  - Soske, Joshua L. (Box 23, Folder 27)
  - Soule, Eugene (Box 23, Folder 28)
  - Spaeth, Carl B. (Box 23, Folder 29)
  - Spaght, Monroe E. (Box 23, Folder 30)
  - Spalding, Alfred B. (Box 23, Folder 31)
  - Spangenberg, Karl M. (Box 23, Folder 32)
  - Spaulding, Hector G. (Box 23, Folder 33)
  - Spence, Homer R. (Box 23, Folder 34)
  - Spencer, David E. (Box 23, Folder 35)
  - Sperry, Leonard J. (Box 23, Folder 36)
  - Springer, John (Box 23, Folder 37)
  - Sproul, Robert Gordon (Box 23, Folder 38)
  - Spurr. William A. (Box 23, Folder 39)
  - Starr, Richard F. (Box 23, Folder 40)
  - Stadtmuller, Henrietta L. (Box 23, Folder 41)
  - Stafford, Walter A. (Box 23, Folder 42)
  - Stanford, James H. (Box 23, Folder 43)
  - Stanley, Edward J. (Box 23, Folder 44)
  - Stanley, Leo L. (Box 23, Folder 45)
  - Stansky, Peter (Box 23, Folder 46)
  - Starbuck, Edwin D. (Box 23, Folder 47)
  - Starks, Chloe Lesley (Box 23, Folder 48)
  - Starks, Edwin Chapin (Box 23, Folder 49)
  - Stauffer, John (Box 23, Folder 50)
  - Stearn, Noel H. (Box 23, Folder 51)
  - Stearns, Herman D. (Box 23, Folder 52)
  - Stearns, Myron M. (Box 23, Folder 53)
  - Stebbins, Horatio (Box 23, Folder 54)
  - Stebbins, Horatio Ward (Box 23, Folder 55)
  - Steele, Charles S. (Box 23, Folder 56)
  - Steere, William C. (Box 23, Folder 57)
  - Stegner, Wallace (Box 23, Folder 58)
  - Steiner, Doris Clayburgh (Box 23, Folder 59)
  - Sterling, Ann Shaver (Mrs. J. E. Wallace) (Box 23, Folder 60)
  - Sterling, J. E. Wallace--Inauguration (Oct. 7, 1949)--Fol. 1 (Box 23, Folder 61)
  - Sterling, J. E. Wallace--Inauguration (Oct. 7, 1949)--Fol. 2 (Box 23, Folder 62)
  - Sterling, J. E. Wallace--Misc. (Box 23, Folder 63)
  - Sterling, J. E. Wallace--Portraits (Box 23, Folder 64)
  - Sterling, J. E. Wallace--Portraits, Informal (Box 23, Folder 65)
  - Sterling, J. E. Wallace--with others #1 (Box 23, Folder 66)
  - Sterling, J. E. Wallace--with others #2 (Box 23, Folder 67)
  - Stern, Lucie ("Aunt Lucie") (Box 23, Folder 68)
  - Stewart, Herbert L. (Box 23, Folder 69)
  - Stillman, John Maxson (and Mrs.) (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Stillman, Minna (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Stillman, Stanley (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Stillwell, Donald (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Stinson, Edward B. (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Stollery, David J. (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Stoltenberg, Clara S. (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Stolz, Lois Meek (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Stone, Calvin P. (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Stone, William E. (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Storey, Parney Hamilton (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Storey, Ruth Tinsley (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Storey, Thomas A. (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Straight, Edith Janet (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Straight, Herbert R. (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Straight, Katharine Haskell (Mrs. Herbert R.) (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Streblow, Lorrain (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Strickland, F. Cowles (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Strong, Edward K. (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Strout, Ernest A. (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - Stuart, Graham H. (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - Stuart, Henry Waldgrave (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - Stuart, William E. (Box 24, Folder 23)
  - Sturrock, Peter A. (Box 24, Folder 24)
  - Sullivan, Michael (Box 24, Folder 25)
  - Summerfield, Lester Douglas (Box 24, Folder 26)
  - Sunshine, Philip (and Mrs.) (Box 24, Folder 27)
  - Sunseri, Mary V. (Box 24, Folder 28)
  - Sutliff, Helen B. (Box 24, Folder 29)
  - Sutton, Don W. (Box 24, Folder 30)
  - Suzzalo, Anthony Henry (Box 24, Folder 31)
  - Swain, Joseph (and Mrs.) (Box 24, Folder 32)
  - Swain, Robert Eckles (and Mrs.) (Box 24, Folder 33)
  - Swain, Stanley (Box 24, Folder 34)
  - Swank, Raynard C. (Box 24, Folder 35)
  - Sweeney, Stender E. (Box 24, Folder 36)
  - Swift, H. Melvin (Box 24, Folder 37)
  - Swinney, C. Melvin (Box 24, Folder 38)
  - Sworakowski, Witold S. (Box 24, Folder 39)
  - Sylvester, Peter E. (Box 24, Folder 40)
  - Taber, Clara Mabel (Box 24, Folder 41)
  - Taber, Stephen (Box 24, Folder 42)
  - Taft, William H. (Box 24, Folder 43)
  - Tarbell, George (Box 24, Folder 44)
  - Tarshis, Lorie (Box 24, Folder 45)
  - Tatlock, John S. P. (Box 24, Folder 46)
  - Tatum, Edward L. (Box 24, Folder 47)
  - Taylor, Alonzo E. (Box 24, Folder 48)
  - Taylor, Donald W. (Box 24, Folder 49)
  - Taylor, Frank J. (Box 24, Folder 50)
  - Taylor, Merritt E. (Box 24, Folder 51)
  - Taylor, Robson (Box 24, Folder 52)
  - Teague, Milton M. (Box 24, Folder 53)
  - Teggart, Frederick J. (Box 24, Folder 54)
  - Templeton, Robert L. ("Dink") (Box 24, Folder 55)
  - Terman, Frederick E. (Box 24, Folder 56)
  - Terman, Lewis M. (Box 24, Folder 57)
  - Thorburn, Wilbur Wilson (Box 24, Folder 58)
  - Thomas, Earl C. (Box 24, Folder 59)
  - Thomas, John Charles (Box 24, Folder 60)
  - Thomas, John H. (Box 24, Folder 61)
  - Thomas, Lawrence G. (Box 24, Folder 62)
  - Thompson, John (Box 24, Folder 63)
  - Thompson, Spencer (Box 24, Folder 64)
  - Thurman, Samuel D., Jr. (Box 24, Folder 65)
  - Tickell, Frederick G. (Box 24, Folder 66)
  - Timken, William R., Jr. (Box 24, Folder 67)
  - Timm, Henry R. (Box 24, Folder 68)
  - Timoshenko, Vladimir (Box 24, Folder 69)
  - Tindale, Keith (Box 24, Folder 70)
  - Todd, Henry A. (Box 24, Folder 71)
  - Tolman, Cyrus F. (Box 24, Folder 72)
  - Townley, Sidney Dean (Box 24, Folder 73)
  - Toynbee, Arnold (Box 24, Folder 74)
  - Toyoda, Hideo W. (Box 24, Folder 75)
  - Trabue, Marion R. (Box 24, Folder 76)
  - Trainor, Margaret (Box 24, Folder 77)
  - Treat, Payson J. (and Mrs.) (Box 24, Folder 78)
  - Tresidder, Donald B.--Portraits (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Tresidder, Donald B.--Portraits, Informal (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Tresidder, Donald B. (and Mrs.) (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Tresidder, Donald B.--with others (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Trimmingham, James (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Triolo, James S. (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Trowbridge, Alfred L. (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Troxell, John P. (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Trueblood, D. Elton (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Tunney, Gene (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Turner, Harry C. (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Turner, J. Howell (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Turrentine, Lowell (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Tuttle, David F., Jr. (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Twitty, Victor C. (and Mrs.) (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Udall, Stewart L. (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Unruh, Jesse (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Vance, Jessica S. (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - VanDenBurgh, John (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Vanderbilt, Cornelius (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Vanderhoof, Vertress L. (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - Van Der Reis, Leo (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - Van Dyke, Milton (Box 25, Folder 23)
  - Van Heyst, Della (Box 25, Folder 24)
  - Van Neil, Cornelius-- See Neil, Cornelius van
  - Van Patton, Nathan (Box 25, Folder 25)
  - Van Sickle, True (Box 25, Folder 26)
  - Van Vleck, John H. (Box 25, Folder 27)
  - Vardac, A. Nicholas (Box 25, Folder 28)
  - Varian, Russell H. (Box 25, Folder 29)
  - Varian, Sigurd F. (Box 25, Folder 30)
  - Veblen, Thorstein (Box 25, Folder 31)
  - Veinott, Arthur F., Jr. (Box 25, Folder 32)
  - Vennard, John K. (Box 25, Folder 33)
  - Villard, Oswald G., Jr. (Box 25, Folder 34)
  - Vincenti, Walter G. (Box 25, Folder 35)
  - VonDerLeyen, Friedrich (Box 25, Folder 36)
  - Von Kleinsmid, Rufus B. (Box 25, Folder 37)
  - Voorhees, Helen Bennett (Box 25, Folder 38)
  - Vucinich, Wayne (Box 25, Folder 39)
  - Wagner, Harvey M. (Box 25, Folder 40)
  - Walker, Frank F. (Box 25, Folder 41)
  - Walker, Gene K. (Box 25, Folder 42)
  - Walker, Robert A. (Box 25, Folder 43)
  - Walker, William L. (Box 25, Folder 44)
  - Wallenstein, Gerd D. (Box 25, Folder 45)
  - Ward, Eugene V. (Box 25, Folder 46)
  - Warnecke, John C. (Box 25, Folder 47)
  - Warner, Amos G. (Box 25, Folder 48)
  - Watkins, Dean A. (Box 25, Folder 49)
  - Watkins, James T. IV (Box 25, Folder 50)
  - Weaver, Winstead S. "Doodles" (Box 25, Folder 51)
  - Webb, Eugene J. (Box 25, Folder 52)
  - Webb, Winifred (Box 25, Folder 53)
  - Weber, David C. (Box 25, Folder 54)
  - Webster, David L. (Box 25, Folder 55)
  - Weiler, Lawrence D. (Box 25, Folder 56)
  - Weinmann, Louis R. (Box 25, Folder 57)
  - Weinstein, Franklin (Box 25, Folder 58)
  - Wells, James B. (Box 25, Folder 59)
  - Wenig, Herbert E. (Box 25, Folder 60)
  - Wert, Robert J. (Box 25, Folder 61)
  - Weeden, Alan N. (Box 25, Folder 62)
  - Weisz, Margie (Box 25, Folder 63)
  - Wentworth, Gerald O. (Box 25, Folder 64)
  - West, Victor J. (Box 25, Folder 65)
  - Weymouth, Frank W. (and Mrs.) (Box 25, Folder 66)
  - Wheaton, George S. (Box 25, Folder 67)
  - Wheeler, Benjamin Ide (Box 25, Folder 68)
  - Whitaker, Douglas M. (Box 25, Folder 69)
  - Whitaker, Virgil K. (Box 25, Folder 70)
  - White, Andrew D. (Box 25, Folder 71)
  - White, C. Langdon (Box 25, Folder 72)
  - White, C. Wadsworth (Box 25, Folder 73)
  - White, James (Box 25, Folder 74)
  - White, Lynn Townsend (Box 25, Folder 75)
  - Whittier, Clarke B. (Box 25, Folder 76)
  - Wickham, Margaret (Box 25, Folder 77)
  - Wiggins, Ira L. (Box 25, Folder 78)
  - Wight, Wm. F. (Box 25, Folder 79)
  - Wilbur, Blake C. (and Mrs.) (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Wilbur, Dwight L. (and Mrs.) (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Wilbur, Jessica (Mrs. Leonard Ely) (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Wilbur, Marguerite May Blake (Mrs. Ray Lyman Wilbur) (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Wilbur, Ray Lyman--Funeral (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Wilbur, Ray Lyman--Inauguration (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Wilbur, Ray Lyman--Portraits #1 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Wilbur, Ray Lyman--Portraits #2 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Wilbur, Ray Lyman--Portraits Informal (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Wilbur, Ray Lyman--With Others #1 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Wilbur, Ray Lyman--With Others #2 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Wilbur, Ray Lyman--With Others #3 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Wilbur, Ray Lyman, Jr. (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Wilcox, Edith (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Wilcox, John M. (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Wilde, Frank L. (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Wildman, Murray S. (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Wilkes, Marsha (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Williams, Donald (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Williams, Elizabeth (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - Williams, Harry A. (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Williams, Horace E. (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - Williams, Philip C. (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - Williams, Thomas M. (and Mrs.) (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - Willis, Bailey (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - Wilson, Samuel M. (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - Winbigler, H. Donald (Box 26, Folder 27)
  - Wing, Charles B. (Box 26, Folder 28)
  - Winters, Dana S. (Box 26, Folder 29)
  - Winship, Walter, E. (Box 26, Folder 30)
  - Winters, Dana S. (Box 26, Folder 31)
  - Winters, Yvor (Box 26, Folder 32)
  - Wohlford, Mary M. (Box 26, Folder 33)
  - Wood, Peter D. (Box 26, Folder 34)
  - Wood, Thomas D. (Box 26, Folder 35)
  - Woodruff, Edwin H. (Box 26, Folder 36)
  - Woodward, Frederick C. (Box 26, Folder 37)
  - Woodyard, John R. (Box 26, Folder 38)
  - Working, Holbrook (Box 26, Folder 39)
  - Workman, Thomas E. (Box 26, Folder 40)
  - Worrell, Harriet E. (Box 26, Folder 41)
  - Wren, Dale P. (Box 26, Folder 42)
  - Wright, Arthur F. (Box 26, Folder 43)
  - Wright, Gordon (Box 26, Folder 44)
  - Wright, Mary D. (Mrs. Arthur F.) (Box 26, Folder 45)
  - Wyneken, Friedrich A. (Box 26, Folder 46)
  - Yarborough, John M. (Box 26, Folder 47)
  - Yearian, Mason (Box 26, Folder 48)
  - Yoder, Dale (Box 26, Folder 49)
  - Yost, Mary (Box 26, Folder 50)
  - Young, Charles A. "Jack" (Box 26, Folder 51)
  - Young, Donovan H. (Box 26, Folder 52)
  - Young, Hayes W. (Box 26, Folder 53)
  - Young, John A. (Box 26, Folder 54)
  - Young, Stewart W. (Box 26, Folder 55)
  - Zampatto, Lorenzo (Box 26, Folder 56)
  - Zimbardo, Philip (Box 26, Folder 57)
- Oversize Photographs, Series 4 (Box E1-E3)
- Copy Negatives, Series 5 (Box 1-5)